ncl.res.in 2016-01-26

# National Chemical Laboratory

CSIR- NCL respects your right to privacy. As a general rule, this web site does not collect Personal Information about you when you visit the web site. You can generally visit the web site without revealing Personal Information, unless you choose to provide such information.

If the NCL web site requests you to provide personal information, you will be informed for the particular purposes for which the information is gathered and adequate security measures will be taken to protect your personal information.

When you visit the NCL Web site, certain information may be collected from you either voluntarily or involuntarily: Your computer or network's IP address, which must be validated in order for you to access the NCL Web site; Information about your visit such as browser type, operating system, the date and time of the visit, pages visited etc. is gathered in an aggregate manner for quality control, security and improvement of our site.

We do not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on the NCL web site to any third party (public/private). Any information provided to this web site will be protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. This web site may contain links to external web sites whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of other web sites and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those web sites.
